rental-living.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy | Irvine Company

#### YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS

August 15, 2016

#### 1\. GENERAL

This Privacy Policy describes how Irvine Company LLC and its affiliates (collectively, “Irvine”) treat data and information about you that Irvine collects and receives from you through applications that run on mobile devices and tablets (“Applications”), this website and other Irvine websites, and other online locations (collectively, the “Websites”), any Internet connectivity made available by Irvine, other aspects of Irvine’s business including offline, and third parties.

The Websites include without limitation: IrvineCompany.com, Irvinecompanycareers.com, CoastalCollection.com, GoodPlanning.org, IrvineCompanyApartments.com, UTC-Irvine.com, OrangeCountyZest.com, FashionIsland.com, ShopIrvineCompany.com, ShoptheIrvineCompany.com, ShopIrvineSpectrumCenter.com, ShoptheMarketPlace.com, IrvineCompanyOffice.com, SantaClaraSquare.com, SantaClaraSquareOffice.com, FashionIslandHotel.com, AquaLoungenb.com, OakGrillnb.com, PelicanHill.com, VillasatPelicanHill.com, PelicanHillMagazine.com, PelicanGrillnb.com, Coliseumnb.com, Andreanb.com, PelicanHillGolfClub.com, ShopPelicanHill.com, HotelIrvine.com, EatsKitchen.com, RedBarandLounge.com, OakCreekGolfClub.com, GreatSlips.com, IrvinePacific.com, VillagesofIrvine.com, Irvine Company Residents mobile application, and Retail Therapy mobile application.

Irvine’s affiliates include without limitation the entities operating the Websites and Applications listed above and other entities that may be affiliated with Irvine.

If you have a question whether a site is a Website of Irvine, or if an entity is an affiliate of Irvine Company LLC, please check the information posted on the site or other material, or contact Irvine at [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com) or 949-720-2000.

#### 2\. ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

Each time you access, use, place an order on, or browse the Websites or Applications, you signify your acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Websites or Applications and must discontinue use of the Websites and Applications immediately. If you provide your personal information to Irvine through other aspects of Irvine’s business including offline, or if you click on Irvine’s digital advertisements on third party websites or applications, Irvine asks you to review this Privacy Policy which also governs information collected through other aspects of Irvine’s business including offline and digital advertising.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Irvine does not own or control, or to people whom Irvine does not employ or manage.

#### 3\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

##### A. PERSONAL INFORMATION

The personal information that Irvine collects about you may include, without limitation, your first and last name, home address, email address, home telephone number, mobile telephone number, employer name, work address, gender, Social Security number, password, credit or debit card number or other payment method, billing and shipping information, order history, preferences for products or services, shopping and entertainment, and financial information that is not otherwise publicly available.

Irvine collects personal information about you whenever you transact business with Irvine, use Irvine’s products or services, rent, lease or purchase property from Irvine, request information or materials, enter sweepstakes, contests or drawings offered by Irvine, create or update a profile, place orders or make purchases or rent payments, communicate with us about orders or other questions, or visit the Websites or use the Applications. When you register to request information on a Website or Application or make purchases on a Website or Application, for example, you submit personal information. Once you use these features of the Website or Application, you are not anonymous to us.

Irvine also may acquire personal information from publicly available sources, social media platforms, and vendors and other third parties that may share information as permitted in their privacy policies.

Irvine may combine personal information collected as described above with information available from other sources (such as other platforms, Service Providers, analytics services, offline records or publicly available information). If the combined information, or any other non-personal information that Irvine collects about you, is maintained, used or shared in a manner that associates it with your name, contact information (online or offline), we will treat such information as personal information.

##### B. NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Non-personal information refers to data and information that does not personally identify you as the individual to whom the data or information relates, which may include data and information that (i) is aggregated (that is, relates to a group of individuals) by Irvine or a third party (“aggregated non-personal information”), or (ii) is not linked to personal contact information (“de-identified non-personal information”). In either case, non-personal information does not personally identify the individual to whom the information or data collected relates. Non-personal information may include, without limitation, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, your media access control (MAC) address, Collection Technology information (as described below), the pages you request, type of computer or device you use, the operating system you use (e.g., Microsoft Windows, Mac OS, Google Chrome OS, iOS or Android), the type of browser you use (e.g., Firefox, Chrome, Internet Explorer or Safari), the domain name of the Internet service provider, your activities while visiting or using the Websites or Applications and the content you access or view, the time of your visit to or use of the Websites or Applications, the pages you visit and the time spent on the pages, your general geographic location such as the city from which your computer or device is connecting to the Internet, your computer’s or device’s precise geographic location when Wi-Fi is enabled and it is within range of or using Internet connectivity made available by Irvine, information regarding the websites you visit prior to and after visiting the Websites or using the Applications, information regarding your Internet location when you see Irvine’s ads and whether you click on such ads, information regarding your age, gender and interests with respect to products and services and information collected through our security systems and cameras.

Irvine automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser as well as through other analysis of the Websites or Applications. Irvine also may obtain non-personal information from you when you visit our offline locations, as well as from social media platforms, vendors and other third parties, such as Google, Inc. (“Google”) and the operators of other websites or applications that you have visited or used, some of which partner with Irvine or with a display network or analytics service utilized by Irvine, and may share information as permitted in such third party’s privacy policy. Non-personal information may also be obtained from inferences based upon the sites you visit, third party data, information you share on other websites, social media platforms and applications, or demographics derived from profiles you create, such as a Google profile.

**i. Cookies and other “Collection Technology”**

Non-personal information may be collected in a variety of ways, but Collection Technology is often used. “Collection Technology” refers to cookies, web beacons, pixels, gifs, tags and other technologies that collect information in similar ways. Collection Technology such as a cookie may store a piece of data on your browser or device, while other forms of Collection Technology may identify your browser or device and/or collect information through other means. When you visit the Websites or use the Applications or visit another website or application your browser or device may be exposed to Collection Technology and Collection Technology may be stored on your browser or device. Irvine may come to acquire non-personal information about you upon collection of the non-personal information or some time thereafter.

You may delete and/or refuse the use of certain Collection Technologies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. You may use the Websites or Applications even if you choose to refuse or delete such Collection Technologies; however please note that this may affect your ability to use the full functionality of the Websites or Applications, and may impact our ability to customize the Websites or Applications for you.

**ii. Analytics Services**

The Websites or Applications may use analytics services provided by third parties, such as the analytics services of Adobe Marketing Cloud and Google Analytics, among others. These analytics services use Collection Technology to collect and store information about you and your use of the Websites and Applications, which may include the personal and non-personal information described above.

You can read the privacy policy that governs Adobe Marketing Cloud services at http://www.adobe.com/privacy/marketing-cloud.html; additional information regarding Adobe Systems Incorporated’s privacy practices can be found at http://www.adobe.com/privacy.html. Your privacy opt-out choices for the Adobe Marketing Cloud services are available at http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html.

You can read Googles’ privacy policy, which applies to Google Analytics, at http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You also can opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics in the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current browser https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Analytics services also may offer certain advertising features, which the Websites or Applications may utilize. For example, the Websites or Applications may use these advertising features of Google Analytics:

(a) “Demographics and Interest Reporting” to analyze information regarding the interests and demographics of users of the Websites or Applications. Irvine uses such non-personal information in the same manner as Irvine uses other non-personal information as described below.

(b)“Remarketing with Google Analytics” to place ads on other sites directed to people who have visited the Websites or used the Applications.

(c) “Google Display Network Impression Reporting” to report how people’s interactions with Irvine ads relate to their visits to the Websites or use of the Applications.

(d) Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via Collection Technology, such as advertising cooking and identifiers.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by changing the ad settings https://www.google.com/settings/ads.

#### 4\. USE, SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Irvine and its Service Providers (defined below) may use your personal information to provide products or services to you, carry out the purposes for which you provided the information, improve our products and services, keep you apprised of events, information and developments that you may find of interest, administer and process payments, fulfill orders, ship and confirm orders, attend to tasks relating to your transactions with Irvine, provide customer service, update account information, post Submissions, inform you of products or services that may be of interest to you, customize the content or functionality of Websites and Applications to your preferences, present you with targeted content and advertisements as further described in Section 5 below, inquire as to whether you would like to receive any additional information regarding Irvine’s products or services, forward updates, announcements, and newsletters, respond to your communications, and communicate with you about the Websites, the Applications, Communications Services, Submissions and other activities related to the Websites or Applications. You authorize Irvine to transmit email and direct mail to you, call you, send push notifications to your device, send you text messages, and otherwise contact you concerning these matters. Irvine limits access to personal information to those Irvine employees and Service Providers who we believe reasonably need that information to perform the tasks described in the preceding sentence.

Any Irvine affiliate that receives your personal information may share it with other Irvine affiliates for any purpose permitted under this Privacy Policy.

Your personal information will be intentionally disclosed to third parties only as follows:

**A. Disclosures To Third Parties Assisting In Our Operations**  
Irvine may provide your personal information to trusted operators who work on behalf of or with Irvine under confidentiality or similar agreements including service providers, shippers, vendors, payment processors, advertisers, consultants and affiliates (“Service Providers”). These Service Providers may use your personal information as provided in the first paragraph under Section 4 above to help Irvine administer its business or the Websites or Applications, including but not limited to assistance in administering and processing payments, fulfilling orders, shipping and confirming orders, or communicating with you about offers or other information relevant to Irvine.

**B. Disclosures to Third Parties To Provide Information To You About Their Products and Services**  
Except for your credit or debit card number or other payment method, Irvine may provide your personal information to selected third party entities, businesses or organizations that may review and use that information to send email messages or contact you in other ways to provide information to you about their products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. These third parties include without limitation residential homebuilders and other businesses. Consistent with this Privacy Policy, Irvine may share questions or requests that you send to Irvine, including those that contain personal information, with third party homebuilders or other parties so that these third parties can contact you to address your inquiries. Irvine, however, is not responsible for the collection or maintenance of information once in their hands or other practices of such third parties.

**C. Disclosures Under Special Circumstances**  
Irvine may provide information about you in response to or to cooperate with law enforcement, government requests, subpoenas, court orders or legal process; to respond to your requests for customer service or other information; to enforce the Terms of Use or the Acceptable Use Policy governing use of the Internet connectivity made available by Irvine at Irvine locations; to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or to protect the safety or property of Irvine or others. Irvine also may provide information about you if Irvine believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

**D. Major Transactions**  
Irvine reserves the right to transfer any and all information, including without limitation personal information, to any Irvine affiliate or a third party or successor in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or disposition of all or any portion of our business or operations (including without limitation in connection with bankruptcy or any similar proceedings).

#### 5\. USE, SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

Irvine and its Service Providers may use your non-personal information in a variety of ways, such as to administer the Websites, improve the Websites, improve navigation of the Websites and Applications upon your return visit, improve the products and services we offer, analyze and develop advertisements and advertising campaigns, provide you with special offers and promotions and determine their effectiveness, customize the content or functionality of Websites and Applications to your preferences, and analyze trends and site usage.

Irvine also may use non-personal information to present you with targeted content and advertisements (including on third party websites) based on your past visits to the Websites and non-personal information collected over time by us and third parties, and to determine the effectiveness of and optimize the content and advertisements, analyze your interactions with the content and advertisements you are presented with, and how those interactions relate to your visits to the Websites. If you prefer not to receive targeted advertisements from us, as described above, please click on the following link: http://www.aboutads.info/choices. Please note that you still may receive standard advertisements from us and targeted advertisements from third parties after clicking the link. You may need to re-click the link if you delete Collection Technology or use a different computer or browser.

Irvine may share or disclose your non-personal information with or to employees and Service Providers who Irvine reasonably believes need such information to perform the tasks described in this Section 5. Irvine also may use, disclose or share your non-personal information in any other way it desires. If any aggregated non-personal information or de-identified non-personal information becomes identifiable to a person, Irvine will treat such information as Personal Information. We will ask our contracting parties to agree to keep the aggregated non-personal information and de-identified non-personal information in its aggregated or de-identified form.

#### 6\. RESPONDING TO “DO NOT TRACK” SIGNALS

Except as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy, Irvine does not alter the practices detailed herein based upon your selection of the “Do Not Track” setting or other “opt out” setting or feature that may be offered by your browser; however, Irvine reserves the right to do so in the future.

#### 7\. PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Irvine stores personal information using industry standard, reasonable and technically feasible physical, technical and administrative safeguards against foreseeable risks, such as unauthorized access.

Please be aware that the Websites and data storage are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond Irvine’s control. Irvine is not responsible for the acts and omissions of any third parties.

Irvine cannot guarantee the security of the information on and sent from the Websites. No transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Irvine to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, neither Irvine nor any of our Service Providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the internet. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

#### 8\. NOTICE OF PRIVACY RIGHTS OF CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Irvine has adopted a policy of not sharing your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes if you request that we do not do so (“Opt-Out Policy”). You may make such a request by sending us an email at [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com) or mailing your request to:

Information, Irvine Company  
550 Newport Center Drive,  
Post Office Box 6370  
Newport Beach, California 92658-6370

When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, which Website, Application or line of business to which your request pertains, and what personal information you do not want us to share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personal information or for processing this request.

If you are a California resident and have provided personal information to a business with an Opt-Out Policy and such business is required to respond to such requests, you may be entitled by law to request certain information regarding disclosures of personally-identifiable information made by such business to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year (“Disclosure Request”). Such a business is not required to respond to more than one Disclosure Request per customer each year, or to respond to requests made by means other than through the contact information designated by the business for such purposes. However, please note that due to Irvine’s Opt-Out Policy described in the preceding paragraph, we are not obligated by law to provide you with the requested information.

If you are still interested in making a Disclosure Request, please send us an email at [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com). In the Disclosure Request, specify that you seek your “California Customer Choice Privacy Notice.” Please allow thirty (30) days for a response, but note that Irvine is entitled by law to respond to your Disclosure Request by notifying you of your right to prevent the disclosure of personal information pursuant to our Opt-Out Policy and by providing you with a cost-free means to exercise that right.

9\. CORRECTING OR REMOVING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION/OPT OUT  
To review or change your personal information collected by Irvine, please send your request, including the Website or line of business to which your request pertains, to [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com) or to:

Information, Irvine Company  
550 Newport Center Drive,  
Post Office Box 6370  
Newport Beach, California 92658-6370

If you want to unsubscribe from an email list of Irvine, please let us know by following the “Unsubscribe” instructions that are included in each promotional email from Irvine. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) business days to become effective. You may not opt out of receiving communications regarding your purchases, transactions, dealings with the Websites or Applications, or technical information about the Websites or Applications.

#### 10\. CHILDREN

Irvine is committed to protecting the privacy of children. The Websites and Applications are directed to persons 18 years of age or older. Irvine, the Websites and the Applications do not knowingly collect information from children under age 18. If you under age 13, you are not permitted to use the Websites or Applications or to submit any personally identifiable information to the Websites or the Applications. If you provide information to Irvine through the Websites or Applications, you represent and warrant to Irvine that you are 18 years of age or older. If you are 13 – 17 years of age, you may visit, browse and use the information on the Websites or Applications, but you may not submit any personal information to the Websites or Applications, and you represent and warrant to Irvine that you have permission of your parent or guardian to use the Websites or Applications and any activities on the Websites or Applications, who agrees to this Privacy Policy and the Acceptable Use Policy governing use of the Internet connectivity made available by Irvine at Irvine locations, if applicable, on your behalf. If we become aware that a Website or Application user is under age 18 and has provided personal information, we will remove his or her personal information from our files. If you are a parent or guardian and believe Irvine may have inadvertently collected personal information from your child, please notify Irvine immediately by sending an email, including the Website or Application or line of business to which your request pertains, to [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com).

#### 11\. LINKS

On our Websites or Applications, you may have the opportunity to follow a link to other sites that may be of interest to you. Irvine endeavors to link only to reputable organizations. Because these other sites may not be hosted or controlled by Irvine, however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites or the content provided thereon. Collection Technology also may be used by some of those other sites. Therefore, the privacy policies with respect to these areas may differ from those applicable to the Websites or Applications and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of each of those other sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected and maintained by Irvine.

#### 12\. THIRD PARTY POSTINGS

From time to time certain third parties, such as vendors with whom Irvine may have a business relationship, may post information on our Websites or Applications. Irvine is not responsible for the content of these postings, or for ensuring that the third parties comply with this Privacy Policy.

#### 13\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as we add new features and services, as laws change, and as industry privacy and security best practices evolve. We display an effective date on the upper left corner of the Privacy Policy (“Last Revised Date”) for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, you should check the Privacy Policy on a regular basis for the most current privacy practices. Each time you access, use or browse the Websites or Applications, you signify your acceptance of the then current changes to the Privacy Policy applying to your personal information collected by us on and from the effective date of such changes to the extent required by law.

Any changes in the Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting. If Irvine makes any material changes to this Privacy Policy, Irvine will provide you with notice or have other communications with you in the manner and to the extent required by law.

#### 14\. GOVERNING LAW

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by, and will be construed under, the laws of the State of California, U.S.A., without regard to choice of law principles. Those who choose to access the Websites or Applications from locations outside of the United States do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws if and to the extent local laws are applicable, including without limitation, all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the transmission of data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside. Irvine may limit the availability or a Website or Application, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area or jurisdiction, at any time in its sole discretion.

Personal information collected through the Websites or Applications and other aspects of Irvine’s business may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Irvine or its affiliates, subsidiaries or Service Providers maintain facilities. By using the Websites or Applications, you expressly consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

#### 15\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Policy or our Websites or Applications, please contact us at [information@irvinecompany.com](mailto:information@irvinecompany.com). Please note that email communications may not be secure. Accordingly, you should not include personal or other sensitive information in your email correspondence to the Website, Application or Irvine.
